<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="http://lotusot.co.uk/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lotus OT - Specialised occupational therapy services </title>
    <link>http://lotusot.co.uk/</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>About Samantha Taylor</title>
  <link>http://lotusot.co.uk/home</link>
  <description>&lt;span class="field field-name-title field-formatter-string field-type-string field-label-hidden"&gt;About Samantha Taylor&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field-node--body field-formatter-text-default field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden has-single"&gt;&lt;div class="field__items"&gt;&lt;div class="field__item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://lotusot.co.uk/sites/default/files/inline-images/Me%20ID%20%283%29_2.JPG" data-entity-uuid="926a016e-b8ce-4ed1-bd94-42d0d5a0a779" data-entity-type="file" alt="Sam Taylor" width="27.46%" class="align-right" height="1438" loading="lazy" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have over 15 years of experience working in a range of health and education settings. I started my OT career in a physical re-ablement service for adults and have since followed my interest and passion working in mental health services for adults and children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have experience working in schools, social care, inpatient and community services. I have worked in the NHS in different CAMHS teams with varied roles providing mental health assessment, staff training, consultation to school staff and professionals, advice and support for parents carers, OT assessments and Sensory assessment and recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My most recent posts within the NHS were Advanced Occupational Therapist roles in an Intensive Support Team for children with ASC (Autistic Spectrum Condition), and a Sensory Integration service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As an Independent OT I offer specialist assessment and intervention for individuals experiencing difficulties such as mental health, challenging behaviour, Neurodevelopmental conditions, sensory processing that are impacting on engagement in daily activities such as self-care, education or participating in interests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I aim to identify specific occupational needs and strengths to provide support and intervention plans to overcome barriers to successful participation in daily activities. I offer consultation to parents carers and professionals who are seeking advice regarding the above challenges, as well as staff training sessions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work in Greater Manchester and surrounding areas. My services can be provided at homes, online, schools or other community settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span class="field field-name-uid field-formatter-author field-type-entity-reference field-label-hidden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;rick&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field-name-created field-formatter-timestamp field-type-created field-label-hidden"&gt;Mon, 11/27/2023 - 11:13&lt;/span&gt;
</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 11:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>rick</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">8 at http://lotusot.co.uk</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
